hellodirect.com 2006-11-06

# Hello Direct

Hello Direct values the trust you have placed in us. As part of our relationship, we recognize and respect your privacy. That is why Hello Direct is committed to protecting your privacy and using the information you share with us responsibly.

#### What Our Privacy Policy Covers

Our Privacy & Security Statement describes the information we collect about you, as well as why and how we use it. We also explain the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. 

Hello Direct, Inc. respects your privacy and recognizes your right to protection of all personal information you share with us, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc. You are welcome to visit HelloDirect.com anonymously. Personal information will not be collected. Your internet address (IP address: the address of your computer) will be logged so we can learn which parts of the web site you visit and how long you spend on individual pages; however we will not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. Your browser automatically informs us of its name and version number; but again, no personal information will be gathered. 

As a part of our continued commitment to your privacy, Hello Direct rigorously supports and follows the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association (DMA). We have agreed to notify you of your right to opt out of information rental, sale, or exchange between Hello Direct and other marketers, and to honor your requests that we not share your information with other marketers in any way. In addition, we honor your requests to not receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from Hello Direct.

#### Limited Information Gathering

Like many commercial web sites, HelloDirect.com uses software tags called "cookies" so we can better serve you with tailored information when you return. Cookies are small text identifiers sent to your computer to facilitate subsequent visits. Most browsers let you define preferences to notify you when you are sent cookies and let you decide whether to accept or reject them. Virtually all browsers let you remove cookies from your computer. Cookies cannot retrieve information from your computer, spread viruses, or capture your e-mail address. Hello Direct uses the information collected with cookies to track site use and improve our service to you and other visitors. Hello Direct does not use cookies to gather personal information about you.

#### Information Collection and Usage

Hello Direct is the sole owner of the information collected on the site, and may collect personal information voluntarily supplied by you when you order products; enter contests, complete surveys, and the like. Hello Direct clearly informs you in advance, and explains how this personal information is to be used. You have a right not to provide this information. If you choose not to provide such information, you are still welcome to visit HelloDirect.com, but may be unable to participate in certain options, offers, and services.

#### Uses of personal information

If you supply Hello Direct with your postal address, and/or email address, you may receive periodic mailings to inform you of new products, services, events, or offers from our trusted marketing partners. If you prefer not to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an e-mail message to [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com), calling us at 1-800-HELLO34 (1-800-435-5634), or writing to us at 75 Northeastern Blvd., Nashua, NH 03062. Hello Direct occasionally shares information about site visitors and customers with other reputable firms. You are welcome to exclude your name from such use by sending an e-mail message to [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com), calling us at 1-800-HELLO34 (1-800-435-5634), or writing to us at 75 Northeastern Blvd., Nashua, NH 03062. 

If you supply Hello Direct your telephone number while ordering a product or products, you may be contacted by telephone regarding your order or orders; we do not, however, share customer or visitor telephone numbers with other organizations.

#### Security

Hello Direct takes all appropriate and reasonable steps to protect all information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

#### Commitment

Hello Direct is committed to the principle of individual privacy, and is actively involved in and supports industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the internet. Personal data privacy is a new and rapidly changing area, and HelloDirect.com is evolving to meet these demands. 

Please contact us at [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com), call us at 1-800-HELLO34 (1-800-435-5634), or write us at 75 Northeastern Blvd., Nashua, NH 03062 with any questions or comments regarding these privacy policies.

#### Legal Requirements

Hello Direct, in its sole discretion, may disclose customer information to comply with properly authorized civil, criminal or regulatory investigations or subpoenas or summons issued by government authorities.

#### Sale of Assets, Merger, Acquisitions, Bankruptcy

Customer information collected may be transferred as a result of a sale, merger or corporate transfer. 

#### What information is collected?

#### How is my information used?

#### Will my information be shared?

#### How do I access or change my information?

#### How do I remove my information?

#### How does HelloDirect.com use cookies?

#### How does HelloDirect.com make sure my order information is secure?

#### Does HelloDirect.com link to other sites?

#### How does HelloDirect.com protect children's privacy?

#### What if there are changes to this Statement or if I have other questions?

#### What Information Is Collected?

We collect information from you that you provide when you login, join our mailing list, register with us, place an order, or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. Also, categories of information collected to complete your order include, but are not limited to, your name, e-mail address, postal address, phone number and credit card number. In addition, we may maintain a record of your purchases from Hello Direct. We may also acquire names and mailing addresses for select mailings for our trusted marketing partners. On occasion, we may combine information you provide with other demographic information available to us. 

#### How Is My Information Used? 

When you make a purchase from Hello Direct, we use your information to process your order and to answer your questions about the status of your order. We may use the information to provide you with periodic e-mails and mailings about Hello Direct merchandise, services and promotions. We may also send you e-mails to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our online store and your shopping experience. If you request a catalog from us, if you register with us, or if you purchase from us online or over the phone, you have the option to request marketing materials from us, and we may send you notices about our merchandise, services and promotions through mailings. 

#### Will My Information Be Shared? 

Hello Direct only shares information about our customers with affiliated companies and reputable third parties to provide better service to you. These services may include maintaining and managing customer information; providing customer services; taking and fulfilling orders; conducting Hello Direct promotions and surveys; and communicating effectively with our customers. We do not authorize those third parties to make any other use of your information or to send you unsolicited mailings. In addition, Hello Direct may share information that our customers provide us with trusted marketing partners. We also may share aggregated statistical or demographic information about you with third party companies in a manner that does not reveal your personal identity. 

When Hello Direct conducts contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys, or joins with other companies to do so, clients who choose to participate may be asked to provide personal information. Hello Direct and the other participating companies may use this information for such purposes as notifying winners and fulfilling promotional obligations, and may also cross reference customer databases to identify common customers. Information from these activities may be used to explore future promotional opportunities or fulfill contractual obligations. Even if you have chosen not to receive e-mail or postal mail from Hello Direct prior to your participation in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey, you may still receive information from Hello Direct in connection with such activity if you register for or participate in it. You may choose not to participate in contests; sweepstakes, promotions or surveys if you do not wish to receive information from Hello Direct or share your information with Hello Direct and the other companies sponsoring such activities. 

If you are visiting HelloDirect.com through a link from another website or search engine, information about your visit to HelloDirect.com may be collected by the provider of the other website or search engine. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these other websites or search engines. You may avoid disclosing your information to these other websites or search engines by entering HelloDirect.com directly into the address field of your internet browser.

#### How do I access or change my information? 

If at any time you want to change or review the information you have provided, simply sign on to HelloDirect.com and click on "My Account" on the navigation bar. You will then be able to change any information stored in your account. Be sure to click "Save" when you complete your changes. 

You can also change or access this information by calling 1-800-HELLO34, or by sending an e-mail to [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com). Please be sure to include or have ready your full name, address, phone number and e-mail address.

#### How do I remove my information?

If you would prefer not to receive our mailings - just let us know. You may submit your request to unsubscribe directly at HelloDirect.com. To access this feature, click here. In addition, if you have received an e-mail from Hello Direct, you may also reply with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line. You may also contact us as follows: 

Email: [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com)  
By Phone: 1-800-HELLO34 (1-800-435-5634)  
Fax: 1-800-456-2566  
By Mail: 75 Northeastern Blvd.,  
Nashua, NH 03062 

Please include your name and address as it appears on the e-mail or postal mail you received from us and indicate "Do not contact me by (e-mail) or (mail)."

Your request may take up to 10 business days to process, and you may receive e-mail or postal mail in the meantime. Your removal request, along with your name and address will be stored in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. Please note that if you make subsequent purchases from our website, we will confirm your order by e-mail, and we may need to contact you by phone, e-mail, or postal mail with other questions regarding your order.

#### How does HelloDirect.com use cookies? 

HelloDirect.com uses cookies to help us personalize your shopping experience and keep track of your order as you shop in our online store. Your cookie also allows us to recognize you when you return to our site and provides you with access to your account information. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your internet browser. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's help section for instructions. If you turn off cookies, however, you will not be able to purchase from our website, as we will not be able to track your online order. You may still place an order by calling us at 1-800-435-5634.

#### How does HelloDirect.com make sure my order information is secure?

The safety of your credit card information is important to us, and Hello Direct has taken measures to protect the security of your online order information. 

Hello Direct uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to keep your online order information safe. SSL technology encrypts your credit card number, order information and personal information before it is transmitted to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Hello Direct. Our site also displays the VeriSign Secure Site Seal, which indicates that the site has been authenticated by VeriSign and that confidential transactions with the site are secured by SSL encryption. 

Once you enter the checkout page, your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. You can determine the security of your connection by looking at the bottom of your internet browser window after you have accessed our website-SSL technology is active if there is a solid key or a closed lock. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https". 

Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use to process orders at HelloDirect.com. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, you can place your order by calling 1-800-HELLO34. 

While we implement the above and other security measures to protect your information, please note that no data transmitted over the internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

#### Does HelloDirect.com link to other sites?

The HelloDirect.com website may include links to other websites that are not under our control. These other websites have their own policies regarding privacy that you should review. Hello Direct has no responsibility for these linked websites.

#### How does HelloDirect.com protect children's privacy?

Hello Direct is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13 years of age. Hello Direct does not sell products for purchase by children.

#### Changes to this Statement

Hello Direct may update the Privacy & Security Statement from time to time. When we make changes, we will post them here. You may wish to check this section from time to time, because by visiting our website, you agree to accept any such changes to these policies. Except as otherwise mentioned herein, this Privacy & Security Statement only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our website.

#### If you have any questions about our Privacy & Security Statement, please contact us:

Email: [xpressit@hellodirect.com](mailto:xpressit@hellodirect.com)  
By Phone: 1-800-HELLO34 (1-800-435-5634)  
Fax: 1-800-456-2566  
By Mail: 75 Northeastern Blvd.,  
Nashua, NH 03062
